Linka-chan, are you starting Big New Land?
リンカちゃん、大ニューランド始める?
I'm still very healthy, so my ears are fine.
まだまだ、いっぱい元気だから、耳は
It seems like it's not enough.
足りないみたいよ
happy?
嬉しい?
Aren't you happy?
嬉しくない?
I'm happy.
嬉しいです
I may never have an experience like this again.
こんな経験、二度とないかもしれない
I don't think it will happen again.
二度とないと思います
That was good.
良かったね
And it was an important experience.
しかも重大で経験できてね
That's amazing.
すごいね
It's amazing.
すごいです
Well then, there's no point in talking like this.
じゃあさ、こんな喋ってもしょうがないからさ
Ah, that's right.
あ、そうだ
Linka-chan.
リンカちゃんさ
Linka-chan, you know, she's very curious.
リンカちゃんってさ、なんかさ、好奇心大勢じゃん
Uncle, it's not an item, but
おじさんね、アイテムじゃないんだけど、
Hey, I've prepared something good for you.
ちょっとね、いいもの用意してきたんで
So, are you curious?
じゃあ、気になる?
I'm curious.
気になるよね
Okay, I'll keep it for myself like this.
ちょっとじゃあ、こうやって自分の持つで
Take a moment to talk to the viewers.
ちょっと、視聴者さんと話してて
I wonder what it is.
なんだろう
I wonder what will happen.
どうなっちゃうんだろう
Are you taking the pictures yourself?
自分で撮ってんの?
That's amazing.
すごいね
Are you taking photos yourself?
自分で、自分のまま撮ってんの?
Looks like fun.
楽しそうだな
Okay, just take the picture.
いいよ、そのまま撮ってて
I'm so excited.
ドキドキ
Yes, thank you.
はい、ありがとう
Have you seen it?
見たことある?
It's my first time.
初めてです
What is that?
何ですか、それ
This is like Viagra for women.
これね、女性用バイアグラみたいな感じ
Would you like to have a drink?
ちょっと飲んでみる?
Eh, already.
えー、もう
Will you stop it?
止めとく?
No, but I'd like to have a drink.
いや、でもちょっと飲んでみたい
Well, do you know the effects of Viagra?
あのね、バイアグラの効果知ってる?
Well, I guess it's better to just drink it.
まあ、単純に飲んだほうがいいんじゃないっていうので
Shall we have a drink?
ちょっと飲んでみようか
I'm sorry if you don't like your body.
体が嫌なかったらごめんね
Do you want to erase it?
消しちゃわるい?
Because that's not it.
あれじゃないから
Give me a hand.
手出して
Look, look, look.
見して見して見
Yes, okay.
はい、いいよ
I'll bring you some water now.
水今持ってくんね
It's like this.
こんな感じ
It's pink.
ピンクです
Isn't it cute?
かわいいでしょ
Cute Pink.
かわいいピンクさん
Right?
で しょ
It's probably, uh, it'll probably take a while to get there.
多 分ね、あのー、行くのに多分ちょっと時間かかるから
Round 2 starts now.
2ラウンド、今始めるじゃん
After the second round started, maybe a little bit.
2ラウンド始まって、 ちょっとしたら多分、
It might feel like it might be a little different.
あれちょっと違うかもしれないみたいな感じになるかもしれない
yes.
はい
Well, you're already talking like this.
まあ、もうこんなくちゃべってんのさ、
Because of that.
あれだからさ
Shall we go?
行っちゃおうか
Because there's a lot for everyone.
みんないっぱいあるから
Who would you like?
誰がいい?
Hey, everyone.
え、みんな
指名選手
The most energetic.
一番元気
Who is the most energetic person?
一番元気な人?
Come on, come on.
さあ、さあ
After all, I'm standing by.
だって、スタンバってるもんね
Who will play?
誰が遊ぶの?
Okay, just play.
いいよ、遊んでて
Play, play.
遊んで、遊んで
Just a little, just a little, then,
ちょっとさ、 ちょっとさ、じゃあさ、
Everyone is there, but try it once.
みんないるけど、 え、一回胸にしてみて
By yourself.
自分で
Just put it over there.
ちょっとあっちにつけて
Stick it on your back.
背中くっつけて
Yeah, yeah.
そうそうそう
Then, when I wanted to put it in again,
で、もう入れてほしくなった時に、
Go.
行って
I wonder if I've put it in yet.
もう入れたかな、ちょっと
Now let's talk about that guy's case.
ちょっとじゃあ、やつの場合になって
lend me.
貸して
I was starting to push myself a little.
ちょっと押し付きだしてたもんだよ、
this.
これ
Yeah, yeah.
そうそう そう
I'm so deep inside.
ずぶずぶ入っちゃって、もう
Where should I finally get it?
最後にどこ出してもらうか
here we go,
さあ、
Well, shall I let him go now?
さ あ、もう彼のことを、今行かせてもらうか
It smells like a great spirit.
すごい精神の匂いがする
Is it okay inside?
中でいいの?
Don't get your face dirty.
顔を汚してもらいな
Ah, let's go.
あー、行く行く
Ah, it's here again.
あー、また出てきた
It came out again.
また出てきた
Should I stand back?
立ちバックしようか
Can you touch this wall?
こっち壁、手つく?
It's standing back.
立ちバックだよ
It's starting to hit the waist.
腰つきだしだね
There's something about death.
何か死を吹かせてるな
Gamma a little.
ちょっとガンマーして
good?
いい?
It's coming out,
出てきてるよ、
a little bit.
ちょっと
It's bitsbits.
ビ ツビツだよ
What should I do?
どうすんの?
Has it started to work a little?
ちょっと効いてきた?
medicine.
薬
It might have worked.
効いてきたかもしんない
Did you feel good for once?
一回気持ちよくなっちゃったの?
Did it come out?
出ちゃったの?
Wait a minute, then sit down.
ちょっとさ、そしたら座ってみて
Sit down.
座って
Come here more.
もっとこっち来て
Bring your feet towards you.
足を自分の方に持ってね
Sit down.
座って
Hey, let's use this as the head, next time.
ちょっとさ、こっちは頭にして、今度
Make it your head.
頭にして
No, no.
違う違う
Make it your head.
頭にして
This foot.
こっち足
Sit straight.
まっすぐ座って
Straight.
まっすぐな
Get the pot.
鍋取って
Good.
よいしょ
I'm so nervous, mine.
しわびちゃったね、自分の
I was shocked.
びちゃった
It's bitchy.
ビツビツだね
first time.
初めて
first time?
初めて?
How do you do it?
どうやってすんの?
I haven't done it.
やってない
You haven't done it, have you?
やってないでしょ
This is the taste of salt.
これがお塩の味だよ
No more?
もうだめ?
Are you leaving now?
もう出ないか?
I don't want to go out anymore.
もう出なくて
Has it come out yet?
もう出た?
It came out.
出た
Is that enough?
もういいの?
It tastes like my own salt.
自分のお塩の味だね
You can do it, come on.
やって もらえな、ほら
delicious?
おいしい?
It's delicious.
おいしいです
It's hard and you can't do it.
固くして、やってもらえない
How do you do it?
どうやってやるの?
What do you want me to do?
何して欲しい?
I haven't done it.
やってない
Is it better than that?
それ以上いい?
Soft
柔 ら か
Because.
い から
I told you I wasn't going out anymore.
もう出ないって言ったのに
Do you like Chanchin?
ちゃんちん、お好き?
Show me this properly.
ちゃんとここ見せて
Chan-chin, are you getting bigger?
ちゃんちん、大きくなってきた?
Yeah.
うん
I can't.
できない
I did it.
やっちゃった
Do you want to start?
初めにする?
Yeah.
うん
Sit down for a moment.
ちょっと 一回座って
Can I break it down?
崩していい?
So, is that okay?
じゃあちょっと いいですか?
Please line up.
並んでもらって
Even though there were so many people, there were only two of us.
あ んなにいたのに、2人になっちゃった
There are now two people.
2人になっちゃった
It seems that Mr. A and Mr. B wrote it because they were practicing.
Aさん、Bさんは 修練だからって書いちゃったらしい
I missed it.
やり逃されちゃったね
But that's it.
だけどあれだよ
I wanted it the most, I wanted it first, I wanted Rinka-chan.
一番欲しがってた 一番最初に欲しがってた りんかちゃんが欲し
Mr. C who was there?
が ってた Cさん?
Mr. C.
Cさん
Mr. C is here.
Cさんはちゃんといるから
Do you feel safe?
安心する?
I felt relieved.
安心しました
It's reassuring.
安心するよね
Thanks to all of you, Ochin-chan,
おかげさまで、おちんちゃんは みんな、
Because it's completely boring.
すっからかんということで
I squeezed it out.
絞り出しました
it was fun?
楽しかった?
It was fun.
楽しかったね
It was a good experience.
いい経験できたね
By the way, how was it like Viagra?
ちなみにさ、 バイアグラ的なの あれどうだった?
Was it effective?
効き目あった?
I was so excited.
なんかすごい、興奮しちゃいました
Are you excited?
興奮した?
it was good.
良かった
Good for you, Rinka-chan.
りんかちゃん、良かったね
2nd round.
第2ラウンド
I wonder how many times he ejaculated in the second round.
第2ラウンドって何回 射精したんだろうね
tired?
疲れた?
I compared it to my brother and father.
兄さん父に比べた
You're still touching your dick like this.
まだこうやって、おちんちゃんに触るんだね
Even after it's over.
終わってからもね
Basically, it really came across that I like dicks.
根本、おちんちゃんが好きということは すごく伝わりましたね
Rinka-chan, good girl.
りんかちゃん、良い子
I have fond memories of my teenage years.
10代はいい思い出になったということでね
yes.
はい
You still have about two years left before you're 20 years old.
まだ20歳には、 あと2年くらいあるもんね
I agree.
そうですね
I'm a teenager, a little more.
10代で、もうちょっとね
Let's make good memories together with uncle.
良い思い出、おじさんと一緒に作っていこう
Let's make it.
作っていきましょう
Thank you for today.
今日はありがとうね
thank you very much.
ありがとうございました
Thank you very much.
こちらこそありがとうございました
see you.
またね
Thank you.
ありがとうね
bye bye.
バイバイ